<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-02-21T21:30:25-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Welcome</title><subtitle>A blog about randomness!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Experience using Jekyll</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/02/21/jekyll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Experience using Jekyll" /><published>2022-02-21T19:50:13-08:00</published><updated>2022-02-21T19:50:13-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/02/21/jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/02/21/jekyll/"><![CDATA[<p> I think if I were to play around with Jekyll , I would get the hang of it more
    but it is sometimes confusing and has been slightly finicky on my Macbook.  I think 
    it would be great to use more often though.</p>

    <p> Harp didn't want to install correctlly on my Mac so I cannot compare it to Jekyll.
        But, I am pretty sure that I will like Jekyll ore because at least it installed correctly.
        
    </p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think if I were to play around with Jekyll , I would get the hang of it more but it is sometimes confusing and has been slightly finicky on my Macbook. I think it would be great to use more often though.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Brandi</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/02/21/brandi/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Brandi" /><published>2022-02-21T19:45:13-08:00</published><updated>2022-02-21T19:45:13-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/02/21/brandi</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/02/21/brandi/"><![CDATA[<p>In my 30's.  Mom.  Wife.  Sister.  Friend.  ect....</p>
<p> Took time off from classes due to bad car wreck in 2015.</p>
<p> Resumed classes in Spring 2021</p>
<p> Am really hoping that this will be my last semester and no other classes just 
    "magically" need to be taken</p>
<p>Currently split time between Idaho and Nevada for my husbands job.  Additionally, we 
    get to travel more as a family because of his job</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my 30's. Mom. Wife. Sister. Friend. ect.... Took time off from classes due to bad car wreck in 2015. Resumed classes in Spring 2021 Am really hoping that this will be my last semester and no other classes just "magically" need to be taken Currently split time between Idaho and Nevada for my husbands job. Additionally, we get to travel more as a family because of his job]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Future</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/02/21/future/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Future" /><published>2022-02-21T19:45:13-08:00</published><updated>2022-02-21T19:45:13-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/02/21/future</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/02/21/future/"><![CDATA[<p>  I think Jekyll would be great for a website that is for bloggers and those that are crafty ( think Pinterest)
    This allows a person to highlight specific topics, crafts, etc.  
</p>
<p>I also think using Jekyll would be great for those that love to post recipes</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think Jekyll would be great for a website that is for bloggers and those that are crafty ( think Pinterest) This allows a person to highlight specific topics, crafts, etc. I also think using Jekyll would be great for those that love to post recipes]]></summary></entry></feed>